Jane Ivanova

Lead Integration Engineer

https://nucleusfox.github.io/ jane.ivanova.work@gmail.com

Career Summary

- **4+ years** of IT experience in full Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), Requirement Gathering, Design, Development, Testing and Implementation;
- **3+ years** of integration engineering: web services development and configuration, cloud/on-demand/hybrid integration platforms, SOA, microservices and APIs architectures;
- **2+ years** of experience in **Salesforce** bi-directional integration: SOAP/REST APIs, custom web services development. **Apex** development;
- **2+ years** of leading **Informatica Cloud Data Integration** delivery experience. Installation, configuration and troubleshooting of IC Secure Agent. Solution architecture and implementation. eSupport cases life cycle maintaining.
- **2+ years** of experience in **SAP XI/PI/PO** (architecture design, configuration, consulting and implementation, development & support). **Java** development;
- **2 years** of experience in **SAP R/3 ABAP** development: Web Dynpro, Reports, FMs, PPF, BAdIs, SAP Proxy Inbound/Outbound, Web Service administration (SICF, SOAMANAGER, SM59), SSL/TLS management (TRUST, RZ10, RZ11);
- Experience in **SAP HCI Data Services** integration: Installation HCI DS Agent, Datastores, Profiles, Processes, Tasks, SAP SSO life cycle maintaining;
- Experienced in **leading international projects**;
- Experienced in working on **Agile** methodology;
- Experienced in working on **Large-Scrum** methodology as a lead of a Scrum-team;
- Team leading of up to 5 people;

Profile

Integration Analyst and Designer with good knowledge of integration technologies and programming experience. Can provide the full-cycle support starting from the very pre-sales phase till the roll-out phase as well as a project technical documentation preparation: architecture design, concept project, scenarios blueprints, project planning, technical tasks, and solution specifications. I find comfortable working independently as well as working in group, feel confident in leading and mentoring others and can take leading roles as integration architect or integration manager in small and/or large projects.

Technical skills and knowledge

Integrated systems: Salesforce, SAP CRM/ERP/BW, SAP IBP, EDMS,

Billing Systems, Emarsys, Electronic Surveys, Yandex-API, DiaDoc, Microsoft SQL Server,

Apache HTTP Server, various SOAP/REST web-services.

Integration platforms: SAP XI/PI/PO, Informatica Cloud.

Programming languages: Java (proficiency),

Apex (middle),

SAP ABAP (previous experience),

C/C++ (previous experience),

T-SQL (some experience).

Protocols and technologies: SOAP/REST (XML/JSON), HTTP/HTTPS, TCP/IP,

SSL/TLS, FTP/SFTP, SSH, NFS, ODBC/JDBC,

SAP ABAP-proxy, SAP RFC BAPI.

DB administration: Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL

OS (user): Ubuntu, Arch Linux

VCS: Git

Salesforce technologies: Apex classes, triggers, workflow rules, custom objects and

fields, validation rules, page layouts, custom settings,

named credentials.

SAP XI/PI/PO technologies: ccBPM/BPM, complex graphic mappings, Java-

mappings, Adapter module Java-development.

Informatica technologies: Secure Agent installation/configuration, DSS, DRS,

MTT, complex mapping tasks, task flows, schedulers, SAP mapplets, REST API, Real-Time processes, SOAP/REST web services, User Guides for Salesforce,

MDM managed package for Salesforce.

SAP ABAP technologies: Classes, function modules, reports, job planning,

PPF, interaction interfaces (RFC, ABAP-proxy, SOAP-services, HTTP/REST-services), BSP-applications, table views management, BOL.

Education

2013 Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology

BS, General and Applied Physics

Additional education

- Informatica Cloud Data Integration Specialist (Certificate)
- Informatica Cloud Data Management Specialist (Certificate)
- Java SE 7 Programmer: Oracle Certified Associate (Certificate)
- Cryptography (Stanford University open course)
- Algorithms, Part I (Princeton University open course)
- Algorithms, Part II (Princeton University open course)
- SAP Sustainability and Business Innovation (Certificate)
- Rapid Deployment of SAP Solutions (Certificate)
- Micro controllers and organization of microprocessor systems (MIPT extra course)
- Paradigm of business programming and SQL (NIX on base of MIPT extra course)

Additional skills

- Spanish basic level.
- Soccer player former faculty team captain and the coach at MIPT.

Work experience

2017 – present Lead Salesforce Integration Engineer

Masterdata / Customertimes Corp.

Leading integration projects in role of integration architect / Salesforce engineer.

Project functions: analyze of business needs and understanding systems functionality gaps, data modeling, data dictionary and mapping building and architecturing data flows. Design solution specifications and highlevel integration documentation. Formulate tasks to other project participants. Working tightly with customer's in-house development team. Leading development sprints and managing functional and integration tests. Project planning, escalation management, cutover preparation, go-live support, holding knowledge transfer sessions and ensuring customer's success and satisfaction.

2015 – 2017 <u>Senior Integration Consultant</u> Masterdata

Participation in all phases of projects: pre-sale, design, build, pilot / roll-out - in role of integration consultant.

Project functions: systems integration landscape consultation, requirements gathering, solution design and efforts estimation. R&D and Proof of Concept delivery, functional and technical requirements documentation preparation, management of functional and integration tests, and support of the production launching, holding knowledge transfer sessions.

Development of integration on platforms: Informatica Cloud, SAP XI / PI / PO.

2013 – 2015 SAP ABAP Developer

Masterdata

Development and optimization of the applications: integration interfaces (RFC, BAPI, XI proxy), BSP-applications, table views, reports (ALV), transactions, BOL.

Development and planning background job programs, PPF configuration (conditions of planning / launching).

Performance analysis and optimization of the ABAP code.

Functional testing, analysis and elimination of DUMPs, work with the bug tracking system JIRA.

Release versions control management: packing and accompaniment of development in the pilot / roll-out phase. Preparation of instructions for users, technical support and technical reports of the solution implemented.